

# SUMMER LANTZ

summerxlantz@gmail.com | 702-858-4744 | Los Angeles , CA 90001

## Profile

Full stack developer who has dedicated over 500 hours of work to advance skills through bootcamps, private tutors, and personal projects. Proficient in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, and more. Possesses professional WordPress experience, an eye for design, and the ability to contribute to any team.

### Skills

- React.js
- HTML/CSS/JavaScript
- JQuery

- Bootstrap
- SQL/MongoDB/Mongoose
- Node.js

# Education and Training

#### **Associate of Science**

College Of Southern Nevada | Las Vegas, NV

The Complete Web Development Bootcamp.

Udemy

The Complete JavaScript Course

Udemy

Learn JavaScript

Code Academy

# Experience

## **Web Developer**

03/2020 - Current

Freelance | Duarte, CA

- Discussing requirements with clients.
- Designing page layout.
- Writing efficient code.

### Nanny / Teacher / House Manager

08/2018 - 03/2020

Freelance | Las Vegas, NV

- Successfully provided homeschooling for children of various ages.
- Directed household employees, appointments, fights, and large events for the client.
- Executed two major renovations on behalf of clients.

**Server** 09/2015 - 08/2018

The Peppermill Las Vegas | Las Vegas, NV

- Headed the hiring and training of team members.
- Worked as a team member to achieve the highest level of customer service.
- Performed multiple tasks at once, under heavy time constraints

2018